today i will get all my money
invest in my idea bro
oops today is eighty-two
eight days left to end the series
die of missing me
tô
going to 1 other city now
see 1 business possibility
cause i'm a hungry man
I arrived here in Paulinha
let's see what I'll get ready around here
you know what i noticed
that sometimes the recipe that works for John
no good for Mary
there is no way my business is geographically limited
I'm a guy who to get my ideas I need
it's on the move man
expensive for carai
no jack but
doing 1 test on the cars here bro
ha ha ha
i don't know what i squeezed here man
seller came to tell me that this car has an engine
I don't know what
liquid injection
brake a b
s and there i
ah I understood what year it is and how many kilometers it is
i don't understand anything about car bro
I just ask a kind of random question
for the guy to see i'm not that layman like that
but i think he noticed vei
I don't know how I turn off that little store here
caraca vei
I got the beer
as it turns off
wants me to leave
our will realize that I don't have any car
that this guy
his trunk,
but it's tiny,
right?
do i do this
58,000 Germans
17,470% entry
then I would see more OR less
in one view
do you know how much I would give